Guide to the Minister to the University (Dean of the Chapel) records, 1940-1984 UA.17.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Former Duke Chapel Preachers (Box 20)
  - Bishop Sante Uberto Barbieri, 1958 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Harold A. Bosley, Methodist, 1956-1975 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Roy A. Burkhart, 1959-1960 (Box 20)
  - Dr. George A. Buttrick, Presbyterian, 1954-1961 (Box 20)
  - Rev. Professor John L. Casteel, Congregational, 1957 (Box 20)
  - Dr. James W. Clarke, Presbyterian, 1954 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Bernard C. Clausen, Baptist, 1952-1953 (Box 20)
  - Dr. James H. Cockburn, 1956 (Box 20)
  - John R. Cunningham, Presbyterian, 1959 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Edwin T. Dahlberg, 1958-1966 (Box 20)
  - Rev. George Docherty, Presbyterian, 1954 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Louis Evans, Presbyterian, 1954-1962 (Box 20)
  - Rev. Maldwyn Edwards, Methodist, 1956-1959 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Herbert H. Farmer, Presbyterian, 1960-1961 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Franklin Clark Fry, Lutheran, 1963-1968 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Herbert Gezork, Baptist, 1954-1959 (Box 20)
  - Dr. J. Wallace Hamilton, Methodist, 1959-1961 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Kyle Haselden, 1962 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Frederick Brown Harris, 1965 (Box 20)
  - Rev. George P. Hedley, Methodist, 1956-1957 (Box 20)
  - Professor Arthur Jeffrey, 1956 (Box 20)
  - President James A. Jones, Presbyterian, 1956-1958 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Toyohiko Kagawa, 1954-1955 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Frank Laubach, Congregational, 1954-1956 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Halford E. Luccock, Methodist, 1953-1954 (Box 20)
  - Dr. John A. MacKay, Presbyterian, 1954 (Box 20)
  - Dr. George F. MacLeod, Presbyterian, 1954-1962 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Robert McCracken, Baptist, 1956-1960 (Box 20)
  - Rev. Lewis Maclachlan, 1960-1965 (Box 20)
  - John Mauchline, 1965 (Box 20)
  - Philippe Maury, 1957-1967 (Box 20)
  - President Benjamin E. Mays, 1963-1965 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Carl Michalson, Methodist, 1955-1962 (Box 20)
  - Dean Samuel Howard Miller, Baptist, 1965 (Box 20)
  - H. Richard Niebuhr, 1955-1957 (Box 20)
  - D. T. Niles, 1959-1970 (Box 20)
  - Bishop G. Bromley Oxnam, Methodist, 1956-1963 (Box 20)
  - Bishop Edwin A. Penick, D. D., Episcopal, 1955-1959 (Box 20)
  - Bishop James A. Pike, 1955-1970 (Box 20)
  - Dr. William G. Pollard, Episcopal, 1957-1958 (Box 20)
  - Dean Liston Pope, Congregational, 1957-1962 (Box 20)
  - Canon Charles E. Raven, 1958-1964 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Kelsey Regen, Presbyterian, 1960-1965 (Box 20)
  - Rev. Henry G. Ruark, Methodist, 1961-1965 (Box 20)
  - Eric Rust, 1963-1964 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Paul Scherer, Lutheran, 1953-1958 (Box 20)
  - Rabbi Abraham Shusterman, Jewish, 1954-1957 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Joseph R. Sizoo, 1959-1961 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Wyatt A. Smart, Methodist, 1953 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Ralph W. Sockman, Methodist, 1952-1959 (Box 20)
  - Robert W. Spike, 1963-1966 (Box 20)
  - Howard Thurman, 1978 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Paul J. Tillich, 1954-1965 (Box 20)
  - Rev. Theodore O. Wedel, Episcopal, 1955-1977 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Samuel W. Williams, 1968-1970 (Box 20)
- Oversize (Box 21)
  - Altar Clothes -- J. Wippell Company, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Altar Appointments -- J. Wippell Company, 1980 (Box 21)
  - Altar Appointments -- Rambasch, 1980 (Box 21)
  - Installation Committee, 1973 (Box 21)
    Scope and Contents note
    This folder is Accession 77-9 and was pulled from Small Collections.